Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Terrible news! Sir, the royal capital! It's under attack!
While the Wizard King was away, invaders launched an attack on the capital of the Clover Kingdom.
The capital burns, its people besieged by an army of corpses.
You're so sure you're stronger than me, right?
Right! Then come on and show yourselves, magic knights!
People are getting killed and standing around talking's not gonna help them! I'm outta here!
Osta, wait!
Just where do you think you're going? We still don't have a grip on the situation!
And besides, what will you do when you can't even detect magic power?
I'm just gonna go wherever it's loudest!
What are you, some kind of animal?
Now we're talking! Wait up, Osta! I'm not gonna miss seeing my rival in action!
It may chafe taking orders from me! Still, we must act now!
I'll go after Leo and the Black Bull Boy, and then once I've secured them, we'll head to the North!
Silver Eagles, take the Central District, where the enemy is strongest!
Blue Rose Knights, you head East!
As loath as I am to take a man's orders, we must!
Golden Dawn, split into two teams! One heads North-West, the other West! Let's hurry!
I hate to leave before dessert, but I suppose we can come back for it later!
Failure today will bring shame to the Magic Knights! Do not let the enemy get away!
Rust!
Tell me, little girl, do you like it in the Clover Kingdom?
Yes, I do! I love it! So please, sir! Please, I need to stop!
I can't! I hate the Clover Kingdom!
So I'm going to take this town, its people, and you, little girl, and destroy you all!
The strongest of the Magic Knights are on the move, and Osta has run headlong into the fray.
All right! Then I'm gonna protect them!
Could I bother too?
All right!
Thank you.
Every time
この空の中で
涙の夜を壊してよ
いつか射す光へ
約束を守りたいな
君に届けよう
Shift of love
Why are you doing this?
Get out of the way!
I knew some magic knight
would show up
but a black bull, really?
I had an undergrown one at that
Get away from her, you psycho!
She's just a kid!
You're joking!
A black bull with a rusty old sword?
You really believe you can stand against my army?
Hold on.
Did he...?
I was so scared!
I know, but you did great
I need you to get behind me now
Okay
Oh, I see
You must be that supposed
anti-magic freak
Heard of me?
Honestly, though
this can't be right
The black bulls might be
the disgrace of the magic knights
But even they wouldn't take on somebody like you
Pathetic, magicless scum!
Kill him!
You...
You won't get away with this!
What do you want?
Whatever it is, you can have it!
What?
Look!
It's the silver eagles!
The magic knights are here!
They'll save us!
And do you see that?
The captain himself came!
Sir Nuzel!
Sir Solid!
Lady Nedra!
We're here
Now everyone step aside!
What are these things?
Nothing we do seems to keep them down!
Unfortunately, it appears I shall have to pass on dessert after all!
I find these creatures have ruined my appetite!
Oh wow!
Whatever these are, they're really gross, huh Char?
Yes, they are!
Just looking at them makes me sick to my stomach!
And call me Captain Sol!
Uh...
Oh yeah, sorry!
Stay back, filthy wretches!
There are just so many of them!
A corpse army?
I wonder if they have any weaknesses?
So cautious!
If you're strong enough, the enemy's weaknesses don't matter!
You're really creepy!
I hope my rival's alright!
You can worry about looking for the black bull boy later, Leo!
These fiends...
There's magic power inside them!
But while they can move, they aren't living beings!
Which means...
To make sure they stay down, we must destroy them!
Let's see how you like this spell!
My flame magic!
Spiral flame!
Go flame magic!
Solinia!
That's incredible!
Steal creation magic!
Go Spider-Lens!
Oh dear, this won't do.
You need to fight like savages...
Though I suppose that's what you are!
At least you can die with grace and beauty!
I'll whip these mindless sacks of flesh to pieces!
Feel my wrath, you filth!
Sand creation magic!
Sand armored guard!
Wind magic! Towering tornado!
My dream healing flower cradle spell
can help if you've been injured!
Any wounded, please come see me!
Wind magic! Towering tornado!
My dream healing flower cradle spell
can help if you've been injured!
Any wounded, please come see me!
Is there no end to these vile creatures?
You creeps had better keep your hand off a shard!
Earth creation magic! Raging Mother Goddess!
That's Captain!
Not one step further!
No one is permitted to touch me!
Briar creation magic!
Corpse hunting briar trees!
How revolting!
Water creation magic!
Slashing sea serpents!
Least magic! Solid mist clones!
Space clones!
Too bad! These dumb roots are hardly worth the effort!
Receive your punishment! Mercury magic!
Rain of silver!
Fire!
This is what happens to those who dare to rise up against our land!
We crush them!
Flame creation magic!
Leo rudeness!
Fire to ash!
That was amazing!
They're so powerful!
Is there anything they can't do?
Wow, they're incredible!
Yeah, I've got you now!
Hey, I know that yell!
What's he doing?
Mowing down hordes of those things with only that sword of his?
So much raw physical power, and what a straightforward way to fight!
You're almost too entertaining!
And that's exactly what I'm looking for in a rival!
My wraith magic allows me to channel my mana into corpses and control them however I wish!
My very own puppets!
But this boy's attacks instantly cut through the mana,
making it disappear and severing my puppet strings!
Is that all of them?
You-you saved me.
Thank you.
I wouldn't thank me just yet.
Huh?
Heh!
You've gotta be a real monster to attack innocent people like that!
Huh?
Well, I'm gonna make sure you don't do it again!
GAAAHHHHHHHHHH!
Number four.
Jimmy.
Innocent, you say.
These people fail to see how powerful I am!
So?
They're guilty to me!
You've gotta be a real monster to attack innocent people like that!
Huh?
Well, I'm gonna make sure you don't do it again!
GAAAHHHHHH!
GAAAHHHH!
Number four.
Jimmy.
Innocent, you say.
These people fail to see how powerful I am!
GAAAHHHH!
So?
They're guilty to me!
GAAAHHH!
GAAAHHHH!
The corpses just keep coming.
Problem is, they're not the true enemy.
Almost done.
There you go, you're as good as new.
There's just no end to them.
They almost had you there, but lucky for me, you came to the rescue.
I'll treat you both to a gelato later as a thank you.
Go, go, go, go, go!
The loveliest flowers are those with thorns.
Miss Spider's Thread.
Water creation magic.
Holy water bullet!
Here you go, Jimmy.
This little brat is your prey.
Enjoy!
Hey!
I'm getting kind of tired of all the creepy stuff you've been springing on us today,
so chill out!
This wound, it's getting bigger.
Excellent.
It seems you're finally starting to notice the unique effects of Jimmy's special curse shells.
You'll find even a simple scrape won't stop bleeding.
So I'd be careful if I were you, Jimmy!
The big sword is too slow!
For someone without any magic, you certainly are a nuisance.
Still, Jimmy has enough curse power to swatch you like the fly you are.
But, first things first.
Jimmy!
Take care of that little pest he's protecting!
You stay away from her!
Oh, yes, the noble magic knights.
Gladly risking themselves to safeguard the people.
Why are you even bothering with her?
There, see?
Defending all these so-called innocents will only get you hurt, you self-righteous fool!
Please, I'm scared!
The little brat is going to die anyway, sooner or later.
So what's the point of protecting her?
I don't need a reason to save someone's life!
Really?
All right, then.
If that's how you feel,
you can stand there and swing your sword like an idiot until your blood runs dry!
There he is!
I have to help him!
You can't even control your magic properly.
Could there be any greater disgrace than you?
You were as good as banished from House Silver for being an abject failure.
How dare you come waltzing back into the noble realm as if you belong!
This is no place for a pathetic creature like you.
Now leave.
Wasn't killing our mother enough?
No, I would just be in the way.
Please help!
Anyone!
Asta's in trouble!
Thank you, sir!
Concentrate!
Ow!
What'd you do that for?
Tell me, black bull girl.
You aren't hesitating because of your siblings' taunting, are you?
There's no time for that on the battlefield!
One bad decision out here could mean lives lost.
Forget your insecurities.
You stand here today as a member of the Magic Knights.
If you join the Order of your own Accord, you must be determined to grow stronger!
Stronger?
There isn't any shame in being weak, girl.
The shame is in staying weak.
That's right.
He's been proving that all along, hasn't he?
He can do it.
And so can I!
We can grow stronger!
Are you okay?
The weak will die weak while the strong live to grow stronger!
Oh no!
I'm still waiting!
Ah!
Huh?
And who the hell are you?
Noelle!
What mess have you gotten yourself into now?
I can't leave you alone for five minutes!
How about a thank you for bailing you out again?
Thank you!
Now that you can move freely, he won't be able to stop you.
So get going!
I guess somebody's feeling better, huh?
I'm just fine.
It's not like I was that upset.
Brats!
Both of you!
No!
You'll die!
Don't worry, Asta.
Your new rival's got your back.
Now go give that brute a taste of your blade.
Get out there and show me what you can do.
Oh, hey!
That was good timing.
Thank you.
There's no need to thank me.
It's my turn!
I'm gonna take this guy down!
I'm not done yet!
It's gonna fall!
He did it!
You're amazing!
I don't think I've ever seen such an unmaged-like fighting style.
You're just fascinating!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Hm.
Ugh.
Huh?
A ridiculous attack like that shouldn't have been able to bring him down!
Hey, Jimmy!
Can you hear me?
Your sidekick is done!
This time you're gonna have to come after me yourself!
Huh?
Oh!
Think you've got me beat now, do you?
No way, boy!
Come forth!
Alfred!
Now, number two!
Say hi to Alfred!
Go and get him, Alfred!
He's all yours!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Asta.